# CRISTIAN MACOVEI

# github.com/cristianmacovei

## Contact me:

macovei104@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/cristiaanmacovei

https://github.com/ cristianmacovei

+40 720 191 084

#### **PROFILE**

Striving to push myself beyond my comfort zones for personal growth, I ventured myself in a self-taught journey of Frontend and iOS Development. A very well trained sense of self awareness has driven me towards evolving by researching, putting my mind to work and encapsulating the very best of what I've learned from my past. Motivation by curiosity - and vice versa - is what drives me.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### accesa.eu — July 2023 - Present

Software Engineer in Test - 6 week long Bootcamp with ISTQB+ certification. Jira, Confluence, Agile (SCRUM) work environment. Testing on Angular-Developed Frontend interfaces.

## IT School (course) — March 2023 - September 2023

A certified Frontend Web Development Course spanning 6 months, diving deep into HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React as well as Bootstrap and TailwindCSS. Certification by the Romanian Ministry of education.

## MBM Lenux Prod — 2021 - July 2023

Manager of the family business - Client and Supplier relationships, production processes and digital marketing and IT administration

#### Telus International — 2020-2021

Customer Support Ambassador - soft skills, patience, art of effective communication, task management and quick problem solving

#### **BOSCH Service Solutions** — 2020-2020

IT Support for this huge company was also very rich in skill-gathering, as I learned how corporate software works, learned problem-solving, time management and rapid decision making.

## **EDUCATION**

## West University Timisoara - 2022 - 2024

Banking and Finance Study

### Technische Universität München — 2016-2018

Computer Science - Games Engineering - offered me the chance to learn in depth algorithms and data structures coded in **Java**, as well as **Game Design** and **Game Engine Design** in **Unity** and **iOS Development**, on which I focus to this day.

#### **SKILLS**

iOS Development: (2018-Present)
Front-End Engineering: (2023-Present)

HTML, CSS, JS, React, Java, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, TypeScript

#### **Personal Portfolio:**

https://github.com/cristianmacovei

## **Certifications:**

Software Testing: ISTQB (CTFL) Certification

Frontend Web Development: Romanian Ministry of Education